<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Drama House</title>
    <link>http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/News_Events.html</link>
    <description>Welcome to Drama House!  The Drama House is a special-interest housing group committed to the performing arts.  The House provides a unique and intimate performance space, complete with lights and sound, which has been home to University classes, student-directed plays, improv shows, Fireside Chats, parties, concerts, and many other activities. Anyone who is interested in the performing arts, from writing to acting to music-making to tech is encouraged to contact the Drama House to get involved.  Other groups looking to collaborate should also contact the House.  Anyone wanting to live in this diverse, art-centered community is encouraged to apply for admission into the House.  See below or subscribe to our RSS feed to keep up to date with events in the house.</description>
    <generator>iWeb 2.0.3</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/News_Events_files/Picture%201.png</url>
      <title>Drama House</title>
      <link>http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/News_Events.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Stone Spoon Baboon Concert</title>
      <link>http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Entries/2008/5/3_Stone_Spoon_Baboon_Concert.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc266758-95e6-434e-ad92-58f34deb8f37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 3 May 2008 21:00:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Entries/2008/5/3_Stone_Spoon_Baboon_Concert_files/artist250.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Media/artist250_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:168px; height:112px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Rochester band Stone Spoon Baboon will be putting on a free concert in the Drama House main room this Saturday night!  They specialize in their own blend of funk, jazz, and experimental music.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Stone Spoon Baboon was formed in spring 2007 by Kyle Veenema (guitar/vocal), Michael Vaiana (drums), and Reilly Taylor-Cook (bass). Roger Charbonneau (hand percussion) joined the band in spring of 2008. Stone Spoon Baboon's strength draws on the diverse array of styles and backrounds each musician brings to the band, creating a new sound that ranges from funky grooves, mellow tones, to down right bizzarre compositions. The unique vibe they create is accessible to the most avid of listeners as well as those ready to party down and dance.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Entries/2008/5/3_Stone_Spoon_Baboon_Concert_files/artist250.jpg" length="17062" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Between the Lines Presents The Senior Show</title>
      <link>http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Entries/2008/4/30_In_Between_the_Lines_Presents_The_Senior_Show.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef6ef182-8aa6-4c43-b180-a13676ad0dc2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 22:00:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Entries/2008/4/30_In_Between_the_Lines_Presents_The_Senior_Show_files/n16649540361_3878.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Media/n16649540361_3878_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:166px; height:112px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Bits and Ted (2) are graduating! And Ted (1) is done with his take five... Let them make you laugh one more time before they go!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://sa.rochester.edu/drama/DramaHouse/News_Events/Entries/2008/4/30_In_Between_the_Lines_Presents_The_Senior_Show_files/n16649540361_3878.jpg" length="17341" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
